It only matters the story they tell when you're gone
The Kid is a western, drama, action film directed by Vincent D'Onofrio.
New Mexico Territory, 1880.
Rio Cutler and his older sister Sara must abandon their
home after an unfortunate event happens.
In their desperate flee to Santa Fe, they cross paths with the infamous outlaw Billy the Kid
and his gang, who are ruthlessly pursued by a posse led by Sheriff Pat Garret.
Sheriff Pat Garrett, played by Ethan Hawke.
Billy 'The Kid' Bonney, played by Dane DeHaan.
Rio Cutler, played by Jake Schur.
Sara Cutler, played by Leila George.
Bob Orlinger, played by Adam Baldwin.
Grant Cutler, played by Chris Pratt.
The Kid is a 2019 American Western film directed by Vincent
D'Onofrio, from a screenplay by Andrew Lanham.
The film stars Ethan Hawke, Dane DeHaan, Jake Schur, Leila George,
Chris Pratt, Adam Baldwin, and Vincent D'Onofrio.
The Kid was released in the United States on March 8, 2019, by Lionsgate.
The film explores themes of sheriff, based on true
story, posse, outlaw gang, 19th century.
The tone is emotional.